mrqe.com 2018-09-05

# Privacy | MRQE - The Movie Review Query Engine

MRQE is committed to protecting your privacy and wants you to be familiar with how it collects, uses and shares your information. MRQE collects information that can identify individuals. This is information such as your name, mailing address, and email address, and it is usually collected when you sign up for or use a service of MRQE. MRQE also collects personally identifiable information that you may voluntarily provide when you use MRQE, that you may post in a public forum or that you may include when you communicate with MRQE.

MRQE also collects this information when you access the MRQE website, when you make a purchase of MRQE-branded products, and when you sign up for or use the various services offered on the website, such as the MRQE newsletters, online polls and games. Some of this information is collected automatically and some is collected only when you provide it voluntarily.

MRQE also collects information from you automatically when you use the website. This other information that MRQE collects automatically does not contain information that identifies you individually. The automatically collected information is information that helps us design and promote more targeted and beneficial services and features to you, the user, such as advertisements you view or select, which parts of the website you frequent the most and which services you use often.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

MRQE uses information collected from you and about you to notify you of service or website changes, to inform you of movies, products or services you may be interested in, and to request your participation in surveys or other promotions. You can choose not to receive these communications from MRQE. MRQE or its partners also uses your information to process and fulfill any purchases, provide you with information that you request, and deliver content to you that is relevant to your interests.

MRQE combines your usage information for the website and all services with that of other users to determine which areas are most popular. By collecting and analyzing this data, MRQE improves for all users. This data, combined and researched, is our Market Research data. MRQE shares it with potential partners, advertisers, investors and other interested third parties in connection with the marketing of MRQE's products and services. However, Market Research data does not include any information that identifies any individual users of MRQE.

MRQE does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. However, in the event that you expressly opt-in on the website to receive particular information or services that are offered by third parties, we will share your personal information with those third parties for those limited purposes. You may remove your personal information entirely from MRQE’s database by following the posted instructions on the MRQE.com website.

MRQE is very concerned about security and is always trying to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of any information about you that we possess. Unfortunately, the internet is not impregnable. Therefore, MRQE assumes no responsibility nor any liability for disclosure of your information (personally identifiable or otherwise) due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond MRQE's reasonable control.

MRQE does not control the privacy policies of MRQE's advertisers, partners or other third parties that have websites linked to MRQE.

If you disclose personal information about yourself in a public area of MRQE, that information may be collected and used by a third party to send you unsolicited messages, advertisements or for other purposes. MRQE does not control the actions of users in public areas and assumes no responsibility nor liability for any consequences.

MRQE does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen, we will delete such information from our records. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information.

ACCEPTANCE OF PRIVACY POLICY

When you use MRQE or any of its services, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and MRQE will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of MRQE and its services. MRQE reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the website and services after MRQE either personally notifies you or generally posts such changes on www.MRQE.com will constitute your acceptance of those changes.
